## Khushboo

**FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER** 

er.khushudinkar@gmail.com

950-168-4952

Ludhiana,Punjab 👂

khushboo-dinkar-822a94125 in

## **SUMMARY**

Working in techologies since 2018 I succeed to grow my programming skills in different areas. I participate in projects which developing applications for Web. I am motivated to mastering those skills and to enrich my knowledge with a new one.

## SKILLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

- Codeigniter, Laravel
- HMTL, CSS, Javascript, PHP, MySQL
- Vue Js , ASP.Net
- JSON, XML

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Web Developer

Chrishan Solutions Oct 2019 - Jan 2021

- Develop e-xommerce web application
- Implementing new features
- Create new API's
- Worked also in testing and solving bugs

### Full stack web developer

CloudMatrix Feb 2021 - Present

- Build web applications and Api's
- Worked in Html, Css ,Php,Vue Js, Asp.net, laravel and Codeigniter.
- Worked on Strapi.
- Responsible for taking care of the user end for any IT related tasks.
- Work on databases such as Mysql and Sql Server.
- Testing and evaluating new programs and API.
- Writing and implementing efficient code.

## **PROJECTS**

#### tmsfalcon.com

#### Full stack developer

- Build Api's
- Worked in Html, Css ,Php and Codeigniter.
- Responsible for taking care of the user end for any IT related tasks.
- Work on database MS Sql Server.
- Testing and Implementing new modules

## Marketing Website

#### Php developer

- worked on backend functionalities
- Also worked in Vue js

#### web.tmsfalcon.net

## Full stack developer

- Worked in Vue Js and Strapi.
- Implement new functionalities as per client requirement.
- Defined problems, collected data, established facts and validated conclusions.

# Hospitality Management Company (UORQATAR) php Developer

• Worked as a frontend as well as backend developer.

- Create database tables for customer enquiries and billing system.
- Made components for client usage.

## **EDUCATION** Master of Computer Applications

Lovely Professional University Jul 2018 - Jun 2020

Bachelor of Science-Information Technology Lovely Professional University Jun 2015 - Jun 2018

**LANGUAGES** 

English Punjabi ••••

Hindi